Font Color "#ffff" My absence started in nine, but it was still okay to/font
font color "#ffff" one in high school./font
Font Color "#ffff" then I was at home at 85 %./font
Font Color "#ffffff" My schooling has been like a mountain and coaster before ./font
Font Color "#ffff" during middle school it was a little on and off with/font
font color "#ffff" absence and presence./font
Font Color "#fffff" It was more in high school as it really happened to things/font
Font Color "#ffff" with my absence./font
Font Color "#ffFFFF" because that's when I felt less safe in school and me/font
Font Color "#ffffff" started sitting at home and I played./font
Font Color "#ffFFFF" and I turn around the day which makes sure you do not/font